//   ---------------------------------------subraction questions--------------------------
const level9SubQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "what is 58 - 9?",
        "options": ["49", "50", "51", "57"],
        "answer": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 12 - 9?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5", "11"],
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 93 - 9?",
        "options": ["84", "85", "86", "92"],
        "answer": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 76 - 9?",
        "options": ["67", "68", "69", "75"],
        "answer": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 30 - 9?",
        "options": ["21", "22", "23", "29"],
        "answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 41 - 9?",
        "options": ["32", "33", "34", "40"],
        "answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 84 - 9?",
        "options": ["75", "76", "77", "83"],
        "answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 65 - 9?",
        "options": ["56", "57", "58", "64"],
        "answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 20 - 9?",
        "options": ["11", "12", "13", "19"],
        "answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 5 - 9?",
        "options": ["-4", "-3", "-2", "4"],
        "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 77 - 9?",
        "options": ["68", "69", "70", "76"],
        "answer": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 49 - 9?",
        "options": ["40", "41", "42", "48"],
        "answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 89 - 9?",
        "options": ["80", "81", "82", "88"],
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3 - 9?",
        "options": ["-6", "-5", "-4", "2"],
        "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 63 - 9?",
        "options": ["54", "55", "56", "62"],
        "answer": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 16 - 9?",
        "options": ["7", "8", "9", "15"],
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 71 - 9?",
        "options": ["62", "63", "64", "70"],
        "answer": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 97 - 9?",
        "options": ["88", "89", "90", "87"],
        "answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 38 - 9?",
        "options": ["29", "30", "31", "37"],
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 50 - 9?",
        "options": ["41", "42", "43", "49"],
        "answer": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 24 - 9?",
        "options": ["15", "16", "17", "23"],
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 82 - 9?",
        "options": ["73", "74", "75", "81"],
        "answer": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 10 - 9?",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3", "9"],
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 52 - 9?",
        "options": ["43", "44", "45", "51"],
        "answer": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 36 - 9?",
        "options": ["27", "28", "29", "35"],
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 87 - 9?",
        "options": ["78", "79", "80", "86"],
        "answer": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 9 - 9?",
        "options": ["0", "1", "2", "8"],
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 69 - 9?",
        "options": ["60", "61", "62", "68"],
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 45 - 9?",
        "options": ["36", "37", "38", "44"],
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 19 - 9?",
        "options": ["10", "11", "12", "18"],
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 7 - 9?",
        "options": ["-2", "-1", "0", "6"],
        "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 94 - 9?",
        "options": ["85", "86", "87", "93"],
        "answer": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 32 - 9?",
        "options": ["23", "24", "25", "31"],
        "answer": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 60 - 9?",
        "options": ["51", "52", "53", "59"],
        "answer": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 78 - 9?",
        "options": ["69", "70", "71", "77"],
        "answer": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 27 - 9?",
        "options": ["18", "19", "20", "26"],
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 99 - 9?",
        "options": ["90", "91", "92", "98"],
        "answer": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 2 - 9?",
        "options": ["-7", "-6", "-5", "1"],
        "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 80 - 9?",
        "options": ["71", "72", "73", "79"],
        "answer": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 43 - 9?",
        "options": ["34", "35", "36", "42"],
        "answer": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 56 - 9?",
        "options": ["47", "48", "49", "55"],
        "answer": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 23 - 9?",
        "options": ["14", "15", "16", "22"],
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 8 - 9?",
        "options": ["-1", "0", "1", "7"],
        "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 47 - 9?",
        "options": ["38", "39", "40", "46"],
        "answer": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 72 - 9?",
        "options": ["63", "64", "65", "71"],
        "answer": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 31 - 9?",
        "options": ["22", "23", "24", "30"],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 68 - 9?",
        "options": ["59", "60", "61", "67"],
        "answer": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 1 - 9?",
        "options": ["-8", "-7", "-6", "0"],
        "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 85 - 9?",
        "options": ["76", "77", "78", "84"],
        "answer": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 14 - 9?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "7", "13"],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 64 - 9?",
        "options": ["55", "56", "57", "63"],
        "answer": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 53 - 9?",
        "options": ["44", "45", "46", "52"],
        "answer": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 39 - 9?",
        "options": ["30", "31", "32", "38"],
        "answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 95 - 9?",
        "options": ["86", "87", "88", "94"],
        "answer": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 25 - 9?",
        "options": ["16", "17", "18", "24"],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 4 - 9?",
        "options": ["-5", "-4", "-3", "3"],
        "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 74 - 9?",
        "options": ["65", "66", "67", "73"],
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 21 - 9?",
        "options": ["12", "13", "14", "20"],
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 67 - 9?",
        "options": ["58", "59", "60", "66"],
        "answer": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 17 - 9?",
        "options": ["8", "9", "10", "16"],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 91 - 9?",
        "options": ["82", "83", "84", "90"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 59 - 9?",
        "options": ["50", "51", "52", "58"],
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 28 - 9?",
        "options": ["19", "20", "21", "27"],
        "answer": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 81 - 9?",
        "options": ["72", "73", "74", "80"],
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 13 - 9?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6", "12"],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 61 - 9?",
        "options": ["52", "53", "54", "60"],
        "answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 79 - 9?",
        "options": ["70", "71", "72", "78"],
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 34 - 9?",
        "options": ["25", "26", "27", "33"],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 55 - 9?",
        "options": ["46", "47", "48", "54"],
        "answer": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 98 - 9?",
        "options": ["89", "90", "91", "97"],
        "answer": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 48 - 9?",
        "options": ["39", "40", "41", "47"],
        "answer": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 22 - 9?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "15", "21"],
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 70 - 9?",
        "options": ["61", "62", "63", "69"],
        "answer": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 18 - 9?",
        "options": ["9", "10", "11", "17"],
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 66 - 9?",
        "options": ["57", "58", "59", "65"],
        "answer": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 15 - 9?",
        "options": ["6", "7", "8", "14"],
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 75 - 9?",
        "options": ["66", "67", "68", "74"],
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 37 - 9?",
        "options": ["28", "29", "30", "36"],
        "answer": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 92 - 9?",
        "options": ["83", "84", "85", "91"],
        "answer": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 6 - 9?",
        "options": ["-3", "-2", "-1", "5"],
        "answer": "-3"
    }
      ];
      function shuffleArray(array) {
        for (let i = array.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
          const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
          [array[i], array[j]] = [array[j], array[i]];
        }
        return array;
      }
      
      level9SubQuestions.forEach(question => {
        question.options = shuffleArray(question.options);
      });
    
    export default level9SubQuestions;